A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Ann C. Whitman - Politics, Series P FA351
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Doty, Robert M., 1967-1971 (Box 5, Folder 126)
  Head of Whitney Museum, re: Art Commission for South Mall Project, other art issues.
- Dougalss, Robert R. (Mr. & Mrs.), 1965-1973 (Box 5, Folder 127)
  Association for Retarded Children, NAR resignation, sends prospectus, "America in the World in the Next Quarter Century."
- Doyle, Joseph (Dr.), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 128)
  NAR heart check-up.
- Dumas, Maureen, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 129)
  Re: management of theater in South Mall.
- Duryea, Perry B., 1967-1973 (Box 5, Folder 130)
  Speaker, New York State Assembly. Grumman Aircraft, appointment to Board of Council on the Arts, allotment for Assembly campaign, Conservative Party cross endorsements, program and departmental bill introduction, tax cut, budget.
- E General (Box 5, Folder 131)
  Eaton, Charles: 1966, contribution to the Capitol Hill Club. Ebbott, Percy: 1972, declines invitation by NAR. Eddy, Spencer B.: 1965-1968, resignation as Commisioner of Harness Racing. Edwards, Deighton: 1968, demonstration planned. Edwards, Harry E.: 1967, contribution. Elling, Lynn: 1965-1971, offers world citizenship, sends contribution. Ellington, Buford: 1965, Hudson River Valley Commission, Atomic Energy Commission, proposed Federal Interstate Steering Committee. Elliot, Mrs. R. Sherrard, Jr.: 1959, sends regrets. Elliot, William (Professor): 1967-1970, Republican Party, "Round Table for the Republic." Ellis, Amanda (Professor): 1966, Colorado College professor, thanks for helping Latin Americans. Emeny, Brooks: 1968, re: nephew, Stephen Hansen, new legislator. Engle, Tom: 1968, thanks NAR for gift. Erickson, Hilda: 1963, thanks NAR for gift & recommendation.
- Eaton, Cyrus, 1965-1973 (Box 5, Folder 132)
  Recollections.
- Edelson, Stuart M., 1971 (Box 5, Folder 133)
  Museum of Modern Art (MoMA) Administrative staff, wishes to see NAR.
- Edwards, Agustin, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 134)
  Re: talks NAR had with Chilean Minister Huerta.
- Edwards, Wayne E., 1972 (Box 5, Folder 135)
  Wishes to stay at Monte Sacro, declined.
- Egan, Elisabeth, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 136)
- Ehrlichman, John W., 1969-1973 (Box 5, Folder 137)
  Information on Lawrence W. Pierce; contraints on Federal Budget; 1972 message to New York State Legislature; recommendations for members of US delegation to United Nations Conference; other government position recommendations; agreement between (U.S. Department of) Housing and Urban Development and New York State for Federal Housing subsidies.
- En-Lai, Chou (The Honorable), 1972 (Box 5, Folder 138)
- Ernemann, Andrew (His Excellency), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 139)
  Incident in front of 812 Fifth Avenue
- Ernst, Morris L., 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 140)
  "Leisure."
- Esposito, Meade (Honorable), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 141)
  Closing Brooklyn employment office.
- Evans, Daniel (The Honorable), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 142)
  Governor of Washington.
- Eyssell, Gustav (Mr. & Mrs.), 1961-1973 (Box 5, Folder 143)
  Hemisphere Club; congratulations on assuming presidency of New York Convention and Visitors Bureau; contribution and involvement to the Arts & Entertainment Committee; Christmas greetings; Milton Rubin; 10th Anniversary of the New York State Council on the Arts; film on the life of (Reverend) Martin Luther King, Jr.
- F General (Box 5, Folder 144)
  Fague, John M.: 1963, U.S. Commerce Department Life & Industry Publication. Fair, John: 1965-1966, testimonial dinner for California Republican worker. Ferrer, Mel: 1959, showing of "Green Mansions." Ferry, W.H.: 1959, criticized fall-out shelters. Fersch, Jospeh E.: 1966, meeting of the Governors Club. Fetridge, William Harrison: 1973, contribution to Illinois campaign. Fey, John T.: 1960, President, University of Vermont. Figueiredo, Assis: 1966, asks about Museum of Modern Art show for friend. Finder, Leonard: 1964, editor & publisher of the "Sacramento (Calif.) Union"; California Republican Party. Findley, Paul: 1962-1967, Member of U.S. House of Representatives, Foreign Affairs Committee; farm policy. Fine, Leon: 1960, lawsuits against 810 & 812 Fifth Avenue. Fine, Louis: 1963-1969, supports NAR presidential bids. Finkelstein, David: 1968-1969, Vice President of the Martin Foundation, proposes a "Library of New York Governors' Papers." Finkelstein, Louis: 1972, ex-Chancellor, Jewish Theological Seminary. Finletter, Thomas: 1967, condolences. Fino, Paul: 1967, asked for a meeting with NAR. Firestone, Leonard K.: 1968-1971, invitation; thanks for gift & for Republican support; art.
- F General (Box 5, Folder 145)
  Fisher, John M.: 1965, President of the Institute for American Strategy; National Governors' Conference, Committee on Cold War Education. Fisher, Max (Mr. & Mrs.): 1968, Romney campaign, hospitality. Fitzgerald, Edward: 1965, District Director of the Internal Revenue Service, exemptions for state governors. Fles, Hester C.: 1962, thanks to NAR for condolences. Flood, Elizabeth: 1966, NAR contribution of Women's Press Club. Flores, John: 1968, seeks support for various projects. Flynn, F.M.: 1967, publisher, "New York Daily News," requests to take photos of NAR & family. Ford, Henry II: 1959, thanks for lunch. Ford, Walter B. II: 1963-1968, designer, seeks involvement on South Mall project. Fosdick, Harry Emerson (The Reverend): 1961, copy of letter to Fosdick from President Everett Case of Colgate University. Foster, William C.: 1962, director of the Arms Control & disarmament Agency. Report of first year. Fowler, George: 1961-1967, Chairman of the New York State Human Rights Commission. Attacks Franklin Delano Roosevelt, Jr. tenure. Pointed letter from Jackie Robinson. Fowler, Peggy: no date, thanks to NAR for gift. Francisco, Don: 1963, enjoyed Morris biography. Franklin, George: 1965, supports NAR for President; sends book. Frantz, Harry: 1965-1970, sends book, articles. French, G. Warren: 1968, Dartmouth friend. Furnas, C.C.: 1966, thanks for contribution.
- Fanning, William L., 1961-1971 (Box 6, Folder 146)
  Chairman, State Insurance Fund, Westchester politics.
- Feldstein, Ronald F., 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 147)
  Wish to marry Soviet woman, emigration to U.S.
- Felker, Clay S., 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 148)
  Editor, "New York" magazine.
- Ferry, Sandra (CLOSED FOLDER), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 149)
  Conditions Governing Access note
  Restricted material
- Fields, Fred G. (Jr.), 1971 (Box 6, Folder 150)
  Republican politics.
- Finch, Robert, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 151)
  (U.S. Department of) Health, Education and Welfare Secretary.
- Fine, William, 1967-1973 (Box 6, Folder 152)
  Gifts for Governors' wives, sends speech.
- Finklestein, Jerry, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 153)
  Former New York City Democratic Committee Chairman, transportation, drugs, New York City politics.
- Finley, Lynn (Miss), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 154)
  Letter to Ann C. Whitman re: Gubernatorial secretaries, conference.
- Fischer, Robert E., 1971 (Box 6, Folder 155)
  Criminal investigation.
- Fischer, Warren P. (Mrs.), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 156)
  Thanks to NAR.
- Fitler, William, 1968-1973 (Box 6, Folder 157)
- Fitzpatrick, James, 1963-1972 (Box 6, Folder 158)
  Chairman New York State Power Authority. Public & private power. 1970 campaign.
- Flanigan, Peter, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 159)
  Thanks from NAR.
- Flemming, Arthur (The Honorable), 1959-1971 (Box 6, Folder 160)
  (U.S. Department of) Health, Education and Welfare Secretary, New York State position.
- Fortune, Thomas R., 1971 (Box 6, Folder 161)
  Chairman Black State Legislators Caucus.
- Free, Lloyd, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 162)
  Institute for International Social Research. Political advice; abortion law survey; comments on Nixon personal notes.
- Freeman, Betty (Mrs.), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 163)
  Governors' Club.
- French, John, 1960-1973 (Box 6, Folder 164)
  Personal notes, Dartmouth Class of '30 party.
- Frenkil, Victor, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 165)
  Chairs.
- Friele, Berent, 1967-1973 (Box 6, Folder 166)
  Latin America, personal correspondence.
- Funk, Charles R., 1972 (Box 6, Folder 167)
  NAR suggests to contact Kisinger's office.
- Furness, Betty, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 168)
  Resignation as State Consumer Board Chairman.
- G General (Box 6, Folder 169)
  Gage, Frank P.: 1964-1967, Head of the Lower School, The Allendale School. South America and Chile. Galbreath, John W.: 1966, John W. Galbreath & Company (Realtors), Development of Battery Park City, New York City. Gamble, Lex: 1968, General Foods Corporation employee running for Congress. Garbisch, Edgar W.: 1959, chairman, Dinner Committee, National Football Foundation and Hall of Fame, Annual Awards Dinner. Garin, Michael N.: 1973, "Fortune," Albany Mall photos for NAR 1973 Christmas card published in magazine. Garrity, J.C.: 1962, Christmas card design. Garroway, Dave: 1962-1964, thanks, 1964 Presidential Campaign. Gates, Thomas S.: 1968, seeks meeting. Gavin, James: 1967, Lt. Gen., U.S. Army (ret.), transcript WNBC television. Gaynor, James W.: 1967, Commissioner, Division of Housing and Community Renewal. Community Development. Gelb, Richard L.: 1970, President, Bristol-Myers Company. NAR asks for leave of absence for employee. Gerdes, Dorothy A.: 1966, saw NAR's Venezuela ranch. Gilloon, James V., Jr.: 1963, Executive Director, Robert A. Taft Institute of Government. Launching pilot program. Ginna, Robert E.: 1966, Chairman, Rochester Gas & Electric Corporation. Dedication of Science Information Center. Giovanni: 1966, Giovanni Restaurant, New York City, thank you for gift. Glider, Victor: 1965, horse trip to the Adirondacks. Goldthwait, June L.: 1960, thanks. Goldthwait, Sheldon F.: 1969, President, Bar Harbor Banking & Trust Company. Offers use of property for conferences, etc. Gommi, Theodore: 1967, Union Church of Pocantico Hills. Lectures by Herbert Holt at the church. Gordon, Bernard G. (Mr. & Mrs.): 1967, thanks for gift. Gordon, Lincoln: 1967, Assistant Secretary of State. Brazil & Chile; thank you on Hopkins offer. Government Affairs Foundation: 1965-1968, dissolution of organization, press release. Grace, Peter J.: 1968, W.R. Grace & Company, thanks, assistance re: problems Guayaquil property. Granger, Lester B.: 1959-1966, Professor of Sociology, offers political advice, information. Greene, Eli B.: 1965, correspondence re: NAR-Soviet involvement. Griswood, Patrick Louis (Mrs.): no date, position available. Gross, Leon R.: 1967, sends pricture of the five Rockefeller brothers from the "Washington Post." Gualtieri, Frank: 1970, Vice President and designer Fashion Park. Making NAR summer suits. Gupta, S. (The Honorable): 1965, Consul General India, re: India/Pakistan. Guion, Connie M. (Dr.): 1960, condolences. Gulick, Luther: 1965-1966, Chairman of the Institute of Public Administration, appointment.
- Gallati, Robert R. J., 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 170)
  Leave of absence, events at Attica.
- Galvin, Edward M., 1973 (Box 7, Folder 171)
  Member of the Board of Hudson River-Black River Regulating District.
- Gerace, Joseph, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 173)
  Chautauqua County Legislature Office. Relocation of Cooper Industries, Chautauqua county employment.
- Gigante, Father Louis R., 1972 (Box 7, Folder 174)
  Appeal and meeting.
- Gilhooley, John J., 1965-1973 (Box 7, Folder 175)
  Metropolitan Transit Authority, offers political advice on transportation policy.
- Gimma, John, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 176)
  Chrysler-Plymouth Corporation. Sends picture of NAR boat, "Dragon Lady."
- Ginzberg, Eli (Dr.), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 177)
  Director, Conservation of Human Resources, Columbia University. NAR thanks for book,
- Glendinning, John, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 178)
  Correspondence re: Governors Club.
- Goldman, Harry D., 1970 (Box 7, Folder 179)
  Political candidates,
- Goldwater, Barry (The Honorable), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 180)
  Arizona.
- Goodman, Roy, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 181)
  State Charter Revision Commission for New York City, Interim Report Draft III.
- Goodpaster, Andrew J. (General), 1969-1973 (Box 7, Folder 182)
  Supreme Allied Commander, Europe. NAR visit to SHAPE Headquarters and Paris.
- Gosden, Freeman, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 183)
  Canyon Hotel arrangements.
- Gould, Samuel B. (Dr.), 1967-1970 (Box 7, Folder 184)
  Chancellor, State University of New York; sends Dwight David Eisenhower letter with paper, "On a New Sort of College."
- Gregg, Frank, no date (Box 7, Folder 185)
  Background.
- Guille, Tucky (Mrs. Charles Brown), 1960-1972 (Box 7, Folder 186)
  NAR niece. School and College; problems re: trust and father's estate.
- Guiry, Don (Major), 1971 (Box 7, Folder 187)
  Executive Chamber State Capitol.
- H General (Box 7, Folder 188)
  Hagerty, James: 1963, Vice President, American Broadcasting Company, Republican politics. Haigler, Ronald: 1971, Dartmouth. Hallauer, Carl: 1963, wishes to visit NAR farm in Venezuela. Halloran, John C.: 1959, thanks. Halpern, Alexander: 1963, wants appointment for friend, declined. Halpern, Irving (Mrs.): 1966, thanks. Halsey, Carol: 1961, thanks for wedding check. Halverson, A. W.: 1958-1959, Manager, Public Affairs, General Electric, bid for project. Hanson, Nils: 1969, Westchester Republican State Committee Dinner. Harman, Dudley: 1967-1968, Governors' Club; Post-Vietnam Committee. Harnett, Joel: 1973, preserve 35 cent subway/bus fare. Harris, John: 1970, Chairman of Board, Harris Associates, construction costs for Rockefeller Center Incorporated. Harrison, Joseph, Jr. (Mrs.): 1971, thanks. Haskell, Harry G. (Jr.): 1959, politics & NAR contributions. Hatfield, Mark O.: 1959-1968, Governor and Senator, Oregon. Hathaway, Stanley: 1967, Governor of Wyoming, re: picnic for Governors. Hawkins, Paula: 1973, Southern Republican Conference. Hayes, Gabriel P.: 1959, Mayor of North Tarrytown, re: General Motors expansion. Haymaker Dinner: 1973, clippings from Joe Canzeri. Hayward, Harold A.: 1963, worked with NAR, seeks help finding job. Heck, Owald, Mrs. (Beulah): 1959, death of Oswald Heck, New York State Assemby Speaker. Hecksher, August: 1966, wants to see NAR. Heinz, Henry J. 2nd: 1965-1968, personal, encloses 1968 letter he sent to Nixon. Heiskell, Andrew & Marian: 1966-1971, personal, invitations, New York City politics, NAR & John Lindsay relationship. Hellmuth, James G.: 1966, [Senator Jacob] Javits campaign. Henderson, Loy W. (Mrs.): 1967, seeks support for "National Women's Party." Henry, Sherry P. (Mrs.): 1967, Special Assistant to Sargent Shriver, Office of Economic Oportunity, wishes to show film on Head Start. Hensel, H. Stuve: 1959, International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) Housing. Hentel, Nat: 1967-1968, politics, seeks NAR support for job. Herman, Robert: 1966, Assistant Director, New York State Division of the Budget. Venezuelan politics. Herrera, Filipe: 1967, Inter-American Development Bank.
- H General (Box 7, Folder 189)
  Hilleboe, Herman E. (Dr.): 1960-1967, Commissioner of Health, Professor of Public Health, personal correspondence. Hirota, Yoji: 1971, Dartmouth alumnus. Hirshhorn, Joseph: 1965, Hirshhorn art collection to State University of New York at Purchase. Hitchcock, Ethan Allen: 1960-1967, NAR thanks. Ho, Reginald: 1961, NAR thanks. Hoch, Paul (Dr. & Mrs.): 1960-1964, gifts exchanged, proposal for Psychiatric Health Insurance Plans for the Aged. Hoffman, Paul (Mr. & Mrs.): 1962-1965, thanks. Hoge, Louise (Mrs. Wallace): 1967, NAR cousin. Holcomb, Charles R.: 1969, journalist. Holeman, Frank: 1967, New York "Daily News," NAR thanks. Holton, Linwood: 1973, Governor of Virginia. Hope, Bob: 1966-1969, Bob Hope Day, Republican dinner. Hopkins, Ernest Martin: 1960, Dartmouth. Horan, Danaris Smith: 1963, thanks to NAR. Hornbeck, Lyle & Olga: 1961, New York State Republican Committeeman. Hornidge, George (Mrs.): 1967, Fulton County Board of Supervisors. Horns, Doris C.: 1963, Republican supporter. Horton-Fawkes, George (Mrs.): 1971, integration, appeal. Houghton, Arthur A. (Jr.): 1960-1967, President, Museum of Modern Art, Museum officers, loans of art works, plans for shows. Houston, Raymond W.: 1959, NAR and Rockefeller Brothers Fund contribution to Red Cross. Hoving, Walter: 1966, NAR contribution to Whitney N. Seymour campaign. Howe, Frederic W. Jr. (Mrs.): 1964, radio show appearance. Hoyt, Palmer: 1961, Editor & Publisher, "The Denver Post," politics. Hudoba, Mike: 1973, round table business group to influence public policy. Hudson, Rock: 1967, NAR thanks. Huebner, Lee: 1967, President of the Ripon Society, NAR contributions. Hughes, Ed (Mr. & Mrs.): no date, condolence letter on loss of son in Vietnam. Hughes, Emmet John: 1960-1970, NAR aide and speech writer, politics, (Reverend) Martin Luther King tribute speech, personal. Hughes, Richard J. (Mr. & Mrs.): 1964-1967, Governor of New Jersey, personal. Huldrum, Kathy: 1971, thanks to NAR. Hull, John: 1967, Chairman, Art Department, Marymount College. Humelsine, Carl: 1971, NAR thanks. Humphrey, George: 1968, sends clippings on NAR quitting race for President. Humphrey, Hubert: 1966, Vice President offers apologies to NAR, thanks.
- Haig, Alexander M., 1973 (Box 7, Folder 190)
  Vietnam, U.S.-Soviet trade.
- Haldeman, H. R. (The Honorable), 1970 (Box 7, Folder 191)
  Nixon Vietnam policy.
- Hand, James R., 1973 (Box 7, Folder 192)
  Westchester County politics.
- Hanes, John W., 1966-1973 (Box 7, Folder 193)
  1966 election, Off Track Betting, appointments, politics.
- Hanks, Nancy, 1959-1972 (Box 7, Folder 194)
  Rockefeller Brothers Fund Special Studies, arts funding.
- Harriman, W. Averell (The Honorable), 1959-1972 (Box 7, Folder 195)
  Palisades State Park Commission, official portraitist for gubernatorial portrait.
- Harrison, Wallace, 1959-1973 (Box 8, Folder 196)
  Personal; Albany Mall; Idaho lava stone; Battery Park; World Trade Center; Hudson Institute; foreign policy.
- Hauser, Rita E. (Mrs.), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 197)
  Proposes a woman for Court of Appeals.
- Hausman, Samuel, 1966-1972 (Box 8, Folder 198)
  Contact with Jewish groups; politics; appointments; Soviet emigration.
- Heidelmark, Julie, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 199)
  Thanks for work.
- Hellmuth, James G., 1967-1973 (Box 8, Folder 200)
  Republican State Treasurer, state finances, state & national convention arrangements, Port Authority.
- Herter, Christian A., Jr. (Mr. & Mrs.), 1959-1973 (Box 8, Folder 201)
  Special Assistant to the Secretary of State, Commission on Critical Choices.
- Hesburgh, Theodore M. (Reverend), 1967-1973 (Box 8, Folder 202)
  President of Notre Dame University.
- Hightower, John B., 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 203)
  Director of Museum of Modern Art; New York State Council on the Arts; Indian, Black and Puerto Rican art.
- Hilson, Edwin I. (Mrs.), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 204)
  Invitation to NAR, party for Frank Hogan re-election.
- Hinman, George, 1959-1973 (Box 8, Folder 205)
  NAR transition into office, state & national politics, Republican finances. NAR presidential politics. New Jersey & Connecticut politics, Congressional contact, personal correspondence.
- Hisle, J. Wayne, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 206)
  Rockefeller Center Incorporated lease with Columbia.
- Hobby, Oveta Culp (Mrs.), 1959-1972 (Box 8, Folder 207)
  Former (U.S. Department of) Health, Education and Welfare Secretary.
- Hochschild, Harold, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 208)
  Vice Chairman, Temporary Study Commission on the Future of the Adirondacks.
- Hogan, Frank S., 1972 (Box 8, Folder 209)
  NAR memo, jurisdiction of Special Prosecutor & of local District Attorneys.
- Hood, Caroline, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 210)
  Rockefeller Center Incorporated public relations director, retirement.
- Hooker, R. Wolcott, 1967-1971 (Box 8, Folder 211)
  Businessman.
- Hoover, J. Edgar, 1959-1970 (Box 8, Folder 212)
  Foreign Intelligence Advisory Board, conference, personal.
- Hopkins, Stephen A., 1973 (Box 8, Folder 213)
  Director, New York State Washington Office.
- Horn, Francis H. (Dr.), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 214)
  Dartmouth Class of 1930 reunion.
- Houghton, Amory (The Honorable), 1966-1973 (Box 8, Folder 215)
  President, Corning Glass, Chairman of the Board, Emeritus, Governors' Club.
- Hoving, Thomas P. F., 1968-1973 (Box 8, Folder 216)
  Director, Metropolitan Museum of Art, borrowing of art from Peoples Republic of China.
- Hoxter, Curtis J., 1973 (Box 8, Folder 217)
  Public relations.
- Hurd, T. Norman, 1960-1973 (Box 8, Folder 218)
  Director, Division of Budget; budget school aid; Forest Hills Housing; health insurance; fuel crisis; Fashion Institute of Technology; personal correspondence.
- I General (Box 8, Folder 219)
  International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) Packing Company: no date, Christmas card. Ingraham, Hollis S. (Dr.): 1967, Department of Health Commissioner, assistance. Ingersoll, R. Sturgis: 1959, NAR invitation. Ingallis, George: 1965, New York State Assembly Majority Leader, Assembly Campaign Committee.
- Irwin, John (The Honorable), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 220)
  U.S. Ambassador to France, NAR's visit to Paris.
- Iselin, Peter (Mrs.), 1966-1973 (Box 8, Folder 221)
  Thanks, recommendations to Dartmouth re: admission.
- J General (Box 9, Folder 222)
  James, Ellis M.: 1965, former Norfolk, Virginia Republican Chairman, re: daughter's employment. James, Stephen D.: 1967, President, Citizens Exchange Corps. Jamieson, Francis A.: 1960, NAR aide, "Percy" Report, personal correspondence. Jansen, F.R.J. Eibrink: 1962, NAR's thank-you for help during search for Michael Rockefeller in New Guinea. Javits, Benjamin A.: 1967-1972, New York State housing problems, art exhibition. Jones, Alexander F.: 1959, Executive Editor, "Syracuse Herald-Journal," Khrushchev trip. Jones, Bertram V.: 1966, tickets for Waldorf-Astoria Annual Dinner. Jones, George M. (Mrs.): 1967, President, Mahoning County Republican Women's Club; sends photograph and John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Creed. Jones, Joseph A.: 1964, international commerce plans. Jones, Lem: 1966, reminiscences. Jones, Roger W.: 1973, party primaries. Jones, W. Alton: 1959, Chairman of the Executive Committee, Cities Service Company, Inc.; declines official political party role. Jones, William Bright (Mrs.): 1968-1969, Dartmouth art exhibitition committee. Johnson, Hugh: 1966, purchase of seat on the New York Stock Exchange. Johnson, Philip: 1960, personal, meeting with NAR and Laurance Spelman Rockefeller. Johnson, Robert W.: 1963, Johnson & Johnson, sends book on Cuban developments. Johnston, Eric: 1959, Motion Picture Association. NAR's thank-you for assistance. Johnston, Ernest S.: 1965, thanks for help with inaugural festivities.
- Jablonski, Lee (Miss), 1972 (Box 9, Folder 223)
  Office of the (U.S.) Attorney General. Federal Voting Rights Act litigation.
- Jamieson, J. K., 1973 (Box 9, Folder 224)
  Chairman of the Board, Exxon, NAR's land in Texas.
- Javits, Jacob, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 225)
  Political activities, appeals, personal.
- Johnson, Lyndon (President and Mrs.), 1963-1973 (Box 9, Folder 226)
  Visit of Mr. & Mrs. Johnson to Pocantico Hills. Visit to Lyndon Baines Johnson Ranch, Commission on America in the Next Century, Critical Choices, Lyndon Baines Johnson Library, presidential activities & problems.
- Johnson, Lyndon (President and Mrs.), 1965 (Box 9, Folder 227)
  Report on Vietnam.
- Jones, Howard, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 228)
  Federal grant to New York State on Treatment Alternative to Street Crime.
- Jones, Leo H., 1967 (Box 9, Folder 229)
  Offering Saber Countermeasure system CM-300, for detecting clandestine activities and eavesdropping devices.
- Jones, Robert E. (The Honorable), 1973 (Box 9, Folder 230)
  Acting Chairman, Committee on Public Works, National Commission on Water Quality.
- K General (Box 9, Folder 231)